fontpalace.com 2018-09-20

# Privacy Policy - Free fonts download for Windows and Mac - FontPalace.com

"FontPalace.com" values its visitors’ privacy. Interacting with our website and downloading the free fonts, you acknowledged have read and agreed to both our website disclaimer and privacy policy. We reserve the right to change this policy from time to time by updating this page. If you have any questions regarding our privacy policy or website disclaimer please click here to contact us.

What information do we collect? 

We collect your "name", "email address" and "IP address" when you fill out any of our contact us form. This information is purely used to communicate your query, we do not store mentioned information at our end for any type of future usage. This website will not share any personal information with third parties. 

Google Adsense and the DoubleClick DART Cookie 

We also use third party advertisements to support our site and to bring you offers that are of interest to you, we have Google Adsense, as a third party advertisement vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our website. Google Adsense uses DART cookies and web beacons which enables them to access (your IP address, the browser you used to access our website and your ISP). This information is generally used to serve geo-targeted ads or to showing certain ads based on specific sites you visited on internet. 

You can disable or selectively turn off "our" or "any third-party" cookies from your browser settings, or by managing preferences of your internet security tool. 

For further information, visit [http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html ](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)

Consent 

By using our website "FontPalace.com", you hereby consent to our privacy policy and agree to its terms. 

Website Disclaimer 

We are checking periodically that all the fonts which can be downloaded from "FontPalace.com" are either shareware, freeware or come under an open source license. All the fonts on this website are their authors' property. 

If you find any fonts on our website that are not come under aforementioned types, or violates a copyright, please email us and it will be removed immediately.
